# **MUHAMMAD SYAFRUDIN**

## Technology Enthusiast

Address.

Guui-dong, Gwangjin-gu, Seoul, Korea.

Phone.

+82-10-8607-1390

Email.

justudinlab@gmail.com



### **PROFILE**

He came from Yogyakarta, Indonesia, and has been living in Seoul, Korea since 2014. He has been working in the field of software engineering since 2009. He used to learn the technologies from books as well as the internet and improve his skills by doing freelance projects. He loves to learn and share new things (ideas, techs, and skills) and very welcome for the challenging opportunities. Currently, he is in the final year of his Ph.D and works as a researcher in Dongguk University.

#### **EDUCATIONAL**

2009 - 2013

SUNAN KALIJAGA STATE ISLAMIC UNIVERSITY

Department of Informatics Engineering Bachelor of Computer Science (B.CS)

2014 - 2019

DONGGUK UNIVERSITY

Department of Industrial and Systems Engineering Doctor of Engineering (Dr.Eng)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

2011 - 2013

SUNAN KALIJAGA STATE ISLAMIC UNIVERSITY

Teaching Assistant

Course subjects: Linux operating system (OS), C-programming, Java-programming, Web-programming (php&mysql), Databases (oracle&mysql), Computer network.

2012 - 2014

SUNAN KALIJAGA STATE ISLAMIC UNIVERSITY

Web Developer

Design and develop alumni, lab, and graduation information system. Technologies used are PHP Codelgniter and Oracle database with NGINX as a webserver and Ubuntu Server as an OS.

2014 - Present

**DONGGUK UNIVERSITY** 

Researcher

Design and develop real-time monitoring system with big data technologies in manufacturing, perishable food supply chain, personalized healthcare, and indoor building. Technologies used are IoT, BLE and Smartphone-based Sensors, iBeacon, Apache Kafka, Apache Storm, Apache Spark, TensorFlow, and MongoDB.

## **PROFICIENCY AND SKILLS**



**PYTHON Programming** 

Real-time Data Processing .....

**TEAMWORK** 

••••••

## **LINKS**



github.com/justudin



justudin.com



in linkedin.com/in/justudin



researchgate.net/profile/Muhammad\_Syafrudin